lowepro.com 2017-09-17

# Lowepro | Privacy Policy

## Lowepro Privacy Policy

_Note: This policy was updated on October 7, 2016_

Your privacy is as important to Lowepro as it is to you. DayMen Canada Acquisition ULC, (owner of the Lowepro Brand) and all of it's related companies and entities, respects the privacy of visitors to its Website. This online privacy statement specifies what information is collected online, the use and disclosure of your personal information you submit through our Website and how it is used. 

#### What Personal Information is Collected?

In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. The information we learn from customers, however, helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at lowepro.com. Personal information includes your name, address, email address, phone number and any other non-public information.

#### Consent

By submitting personal information through our Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your personal information according to this Privacy Policy.

#### Information You Give Us: 

DayMen Canada Acquisition ULC, it's related companies and entities and its third party service providers, receive and store personal information about you when you subscribe to a service, register to receive brochures, or participate in contests, sweepstakes and/or promotions. This information may include your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number and email address. You may choose not to provide such information.

#### How is Information Used?

Emails: If you provide the lowepro.com web site with your e–mail address, you may receive e–mails from the lowepro.com web site. If you do not want to receive marketing or promotional e–mails from our web site, please click here.

Catalog Mailing List: If you consent and provide your name and address, we will add you to our mailing list and we may send you our Lowepro brochures as a result of visiting our web site. If you prefer not to receive any of these brochures from us, please click here.

If you provide feedback on any of our products and services to us, or comment in a forum or provide and review, we may use such feedback and comments for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your personal information.

Sharing with Other Companies: Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share personal information with third parties and we will not disclose financial information.

We do share information with organizations that provide support services to us directly. We carefully select our Third Party Service Providers such as vendors, business partners and other organizations (such as printers, mailing houses, web hosts, order fulfillment, shipping, customer service, data management and promotional services) or that help us market our products and services. We provide these companies with the information as needed for them to perform their functions. 

#### Security

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal and financial information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

#### Links to Third Party Sites

The lowepro.com web site may include links to other web sites that are not under our control. These other web sites have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies before visiting those websites. 

A link to an outside website does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents.

#### Cookie Policy

Lowepro.com uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored in your web browser that allows Lowepro, it's related companies and entities or a third party to recognize you. Cookies might be used for the following purposes: (1) to enable certain functions; (2) to provide analytics; (3) to store your preferences and customize your experience; and (4) to enable ad delivery and behavioral advertising.

#### Policy Changes

This policy is subject to change. If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our web site.
